A Much Married Woman Who Drifts From Husband to Husband!
The Pumpkin Eater is a drama film directed by Jack Clayton.
Jo, the mother of seven children, divorces her second husband in order to
marry Jake, a successful but promiscuous screenwriter.
Though they are physically and emotionally
compatible, they are slowly torn apart.
Jo Armitage, played by Anne Bancroft.
Jake Armitage, played by Peter Finch.
Bob Conway, played by James Mason.
Beth Conway, played by Janine Gray.
Mr. James - Jo's father, played by Cedric Hardwicke.
Mrs. James - Jo's mother, played by Rosalind Atkinson.
The Pumpkin Eater is a 1964 British drama film directed by Jack
Clayton and starring Anne Bancroft and Peter Finch.
The film was adapted by Harold Pinter from the 1962 novel
of the same title by Penelope Mortimer.
The title is a reference to the nursery rhyme "Peter Peter Pumpkin Eater".
The tone is emotional.